www.police.uk 2005-12-10

# The UK Police Service - Privacy and Copyright Policy

## The Data Protection Act

Under the Data Protection Act, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. We use leading technologies and encryption software to safeguard your data, and keep strict security standards to prevent any unauthorised access to it. 

Any personal information entered by you is used exclusively by PITO for the sole purpose of providing you with requested information or services described on this site. We do not pass on personal information to any third parties, outside organisations or individuals except with your express consent. 

You have a right to know about the personal information PITO holds about you in connection with this site. You also have the right to have your data corrected or deleted. 

## Site usage information

### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of data that are often created when you visit a website, and which are stored in the cookie directory of your computer. The cookies do not contain any personal information about you, and they cannot be used to identify an individual user. You can set your browser not to accept cookies . PITO does not send or store cookies from this website. 

### Log files

Log files allow us to record visitors' use of the site. We use this to assess usage and gain management information to make changes to the layout of the website and to the information in it. 

Log files do not contain any personal information and they are not used to identify any individual patterns of use of the site. 

## What happens when I link to another site?

Police.uk links to other websites, both of Police Forces and of other organisations in this country and abroad. This privacy policy applies only to our site, so you should always be aware when you are moving to another site and read the privacy statement of any site which collects personal information. 

We do not pass on any personal information you have given us to any other site. 

## Changes to this privacy policy

If this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. 

## Copyright 2002-4

Material featured on this site is subject to Crown copyright protection unless otherwise indicated. The Crown copyright protected material may be reproduced free of charge in any format or media without requiring specific permission. This is subject to the material being reproduced accurately and not being used in a derogatory manner or in a misleading context. Where the material is being published or issued to others, the source and copyright status must be acknowledged. 

The permission to reproduce Crown copyright protected material does not extend to any material on this site which is identified as being the copyright of a third party. Authorisation to reproduce such material must be obtained from the copyright holders concerned. 

For further details on the licensing of Crown copyright, see current guidance issued by HMSO and the Queen's Printer for Scotland. 

top
